解决方法是我们需要调用
The solution is that we need to call
Fragment.setHasOptionsMenu(true)。做完这步之后，我们将
Fragment.setHasOptionsMenu(true). That way, we'll
在 Fragment 中获得合适的菜单回调方法
get appropriate options menu callback
这样我们能够
methods in the fragment, so that we can
扩展出菜单，并且处理菜单
inflate the menu and for when a menu item
被选择时的事件。这是Fragment扩展菜单的
is selected. And this is where the fragment
地方。记得在 ForecaseFragment 类中，
inflates the menu. Remember from before that in the
我们有一个公开的空构造方法，并且
ForecastFragment class, we have a public empty constructor, and
我们也重写了 onCreateView()方法。我们也在这定义了 FetchWeatherTask类。
we also override onCreateView? We also define FetchWeatherTask here.
现在，我们要重写一个另外的fragment的
Now, we're going to overide an additional fragment life
生命周期方法 onCreate()。这是fragment被创建的地方。
cycle method called onCreate. This is where the fragment
这个方法在 onCreateView() 方法之前执行，
is created, and this happens before the onCreateView
也就是在 UI 被初始化之前执行。因此，
method, which is where the UI gets initialized. So, in
在onCreate()中，我们调用setHasOptionsMenu()并设为true是为了
onCreate, we're going to call setHasOptionsMenu to be true to
表示我们想这些方法的回调。
indicate that we want call backs for these methods.
当onCreateOptionsMenu()被调用时，我们将扩展我们之前定义的
When onCreateOptionsMenu is called, we're going to inflate the menu
叫做 forecasefragment 的菜单布局。在某个菜单被选中的时候
layout that we defined earlier called forecastfragment. We'll also
我们会得到回调通知。当一个
get notified when a menu item is selected. When a menu item with
id为action_refresh的菜单项被调用时，我们暂时
id action_refresh is called, we're going to
在这里返回true。在稍后的课程中，我们将更加细致地
return true for now. We're going to go
学习Activity和Fragment的生命周期方法。
over the activity and fragment life cycle methods in more detail in later
但是如果你想的话，你现在就可以阅读下面的链接所指向的文档。
lessons, but if you want, you can read the documentation linked below for now.